Hey, Poochie, were you aware?
An average of 40,000 people
visit the Louvre per day.
It's the most State museum on Earth.
It opened August 10th, 1793.
So this guarantees that every single
day, it's the most State museum on Earth.
before they decide to
leave the museum behind
40,000 humans will choose
to see the Mona Lisa
and Venus de Milo
fascinating no when you say
fascinating do you mean
the numbers let me clarify
I'm marveling about how
brilliant artists can
imbue their very souls
into something seen as
merely cold and inanimate
as if there stands
the travel beyond time
itself wouldn't you agree
An intriguing thought, I admit.
So you're implying that Leonardo da Venice
and Alexandros of Antioch are stand-users?
Yes.
I'm talking about you as well, Pucci.
Your palesnake has the ability to
wholly manifest souls and preserve them.
What I'm saying is, are you
going to betray me someday?
Why haven't you attacked me yet?
You do know that my
weakness is the sunlight,
which is why I sleep all day in darkness.
You could easily kill me in my sleep.
If you take the world by turning it into
a disc, you can be king almost instantly.
Go ahead.
That's never crossed my
mind even once before.
I have only admiration for people
who help nurture my growth.
You are the king of kings.
When it's over, where will you be?
I want to see it through to the end.
I love you with the same reverence
and passion as I love God.
Forgive me.
It's quite obvious now I've insulted you.
I never imagined I would
one day meet a human who
could so effortlessly put
me at ease in conversation.
You must understand I was afraid of losing
you you'll become a noble priest one day.
I'm certain take that disc do
as you will a token of apology.
I have released it from my body
to you no matter where you may be.
You can be secure in knowing
I will always give you power.
Listen to me, Pale Snake.
Read the memories on that disc
and find out where Jolene is.
Talk to me.
What happened? Is that you?
Answer me, or can't you hear me?
Why is there a radio
randomly sitting here?
Who's the guy talking?
I need to know.
But who the hell is that? Who?
Who?
Oh, of course.
I understand now.
It's a situation where you can't respond.
I just left the medical
wing. That bastard!
It's weather forecast!
I knew it!
Wait, why is it raining now?
I must get the disk!
Damn, you bitch!
She must have gotten weather
forecasts to create this storm!
I'm coming after you!
You're not going anywhere!
What's going on?
I can't see a thing.
Where did you go?
No.
Now there's fog, too.
There is a pattern to the
sound of those rocks pounding.
It's Morsecoe, decipher it.
This fog isn't thick enough.
They're gonna catch me.
Hellsnake's true identity
is Father Poochie.
He knows now.
That little wretch blew my cover.
Weather Forecast knows who I am.
Five hundred three Count the prime numbers
Five oh nine Five hundred twenty-one
All prime numbers and they can't be
divided The reason people succumb to defeat
Five twenty-three Is because of their
shame Shame so great it can kill them
Five Fortun Because of shame, guilt,
and disgrace that make
one regret their past
actions people become
helpless and weak and cave in
it wasn't a mistake
that i didn't notice the
guards radio it was a
trial i'll have to use
what i've learned to
ensure victory the only
saving grace now is jolene
kujo still doesn't know
who i really am therefore
it seems nothing has
meaningfully changed
yet i haven't completely
lost sight of her the
genuine victor is the one
who can conquer and
control all living beings
You managed to make it out alive.
Weather forecast!
Where are Jolene and the rest of them?
Anastasia, I want you to know I
owe you a huge debt of gratitude.
So thank you.
You are why I made it this far.
But still, why would you
go through all this for me?
Finding out Palesnake's
true identity and taking
back my dad's memories
is only my business.
Jolene, how do you still
not know the answer?
I've made my feelings for you clear.
You've been amenable
to my company, mostly.
I see it in your eyes.
Hope that I've never seen
outside nor inside prison.
That's the real reason I'm here.
This thing is chewing on my hair.
Why is it doing that?
Sorry, but I don't know.
You have no idea?
You can see it's chomping
my hair like noodles.
And now it's eating dirt, too.
Maybe it really is a plan
after all. Feeding itself?
But then it falls asleep instantly.
Shh, Jolene, get down.
Something's coming over.
There's two of them, and they've already
gotten way too close for comfort.
FF, it's you!
Jolene, I finally found out
who the real pale snake is.
And it's Father Poochie. Seriously.
He is the one who did this to me.
I almost bit the dust.
If Father Forecast hadn't
shown up, I'd be dead for sure.
FF!
I'm okay, just had to ditch the skin.
Were you guys able to handle your side?
What happened to your right eye?
Here.
Let me see.
I'll treat it for you.
Back up.
What you just said before.
Yeah, that asshole priest.
He was trying to find the baby, but
this time using D &G's memories.
All we have to do now is hunt him down.
With weather forecast too.
Victories are on the corner.
Weather forecast?
Jolene.
Have all your wounds from
the factory healed up now?
Yeah. And yours?
Excuse me, but what is
suddenly happening here?
What do they think they're doing?
Hugging, you dumbass.
I know, that was rhetorical.
FF, go separate them. I mean it.
Pull them apart right now.
You want me to do it?
Well, I certainly can't do it.
Besides, we made a deal
that you would help.
Now hurry, he's getting
his scent all over her.
Oh, cool it, Crisscross.
They're just saying hi to each other.
See?
They're finished.
Quit getting your panties in a bunch.
We found out Father Poochie is the enemy,
so save your tangent
for another time, buddy.
Pardon?
But are you actually talking back?
What gives you the audacity?
It seems you've totally
abandoned our contract.
You're nothing but lowly plankton.
Jolene,
now that we know Pale Snake's identity,
let's dispatch our tiny companion, yes?
There's no need for it,
so I'll go handle it.
All I need now is your
consent, Jolene. Hey, wait!
This pathetic creature isn't an ally.
It's not even human.
As far as I'm concerned,
it shouldn't even exist.
It's lower than creeping fungus
on a rock born as a mistake.
Who knows what evil it
could be capable of.
We can't risk it.
Give me your consent. Hey!
Hold up, tough guy!
Are you talking shit about me?
You should really watch your mouth
or - Get your filthy hands off me!
Now isn't the time for
your nonsense, Plankton.
Weather forecast.
You understand the situation.
I want your consent as well.
Sorry.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Because you're the one who's going to die.
FF, I don't think you know
who you brought with you!
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
No, you've really done it!
Anastasia!
No way! Seriously?
He isn't Weather Forecast.
I think this guy, this
guy is just an illusion.
Thanks for leading the way for me, FF.
Very nice of you.
I'm glad I could make it
with plenty of time before
the real weather forecast
could ruin everything!
547, 557, prime numbers are
unbreakable and indivisible.
I never believed this
day would truly come.
After 22 years, the place that exists
beyond the pinnacle of human achievement.
It's real. This is it.
I knew it.
After decades of searching,
I finally found it.
The direct path to heaven.
True, it's still imperfect and premature.
But all that's left now is to follow
the memory sealed by Jotaro Kujo.
There is a new moon tonight.
Dio!
I will awaken you and
it will be time for a
heaven gloriously fitting
for me to control.
The 36 jammed souls of those who
once committed heinous crimes.
The pure new being born from that soil.
Behold the living embodiment right here.
Though, of course, very quickly
before we get into that.
I must cast you into the
perfect oblivion of death.
You must know it was
always leading up to this.
Get up, daughter of Jotaro.
You're the only one who barely
protected your vital point.
Shame on you.
If you won't come to me, I'll indulge
your stubbornness and come to you!
Pale snake, you piece of shit.
I know who you are now,
but I never once thought I would
find out the way that I did.
Especially meeting you
again now, like this.
You have three big things
I plan to take back.
One, my dad's memories.
Two, the disc you stole from FF's head.
And most importantly, your life.
Why would you possibly
use handcuffs on me?
This your first time in cuffs?
Well, thanks to your dirty little scheme,
I've been wearing them practically
every day since I was dragged here.
You think these measly bracelets
can contain me, do you?
What do you think handcuffs are for?
They're not for preventing
escape, criminal.
They're for forcing your surrender.
I feel compelled to mention you don't
quite seem to understand what you're doing.
See, these handcuffs put us
in straight mutual contact.
So I'm curious to know
what you think it's about.
Exactly which one of us
is being captured here.
Do you follow me?
Your treasured stone ocean stand
has just been turned into a disk.
I can easily coax it out of you. Watch me.
Now do you understand?
When it all boils down, which one of us is
an irretrievably dire strait? You or me?
Whatever.
I don't understand it one bit.
At least that's what I've come to realize.
A few millimeters.
A few millimeters and
this will all be over.
I'm saying that's literally all the forward
movement towards you I'd need right now.
And I can bash your face in.
Imagine swallows that fly
straight into cliffs so they die.
It's impractical and tragic,
but they fly at skewed,
dangerous angles almost
sure to get them killed.
Their parents never taught
them to fly in safe loops.
But it isn't because the
parents chose not to teach them.
It's because they're unable to teach them,
since they've never learned
from their parents either.
Many swallows don't live very long.
They don't even realize they're
predisposed to those fatal accidents.
I believe Jotaro was just such a swallow.
Finally, your stone ocean is mine!
But how did she know when I blinded
her with the disc it doesn't make sense
is she feeling it from These cuffs
vibrations oh I see it's intimidation
that's it she's using intimidation
to detect and Fend off my attacks
I didn't think she even possessed
damn powers when she arrived at the
prison.
I thought she was just a pathetic girl,
wasting her tears on a man who deceived
her.
This is bad.
This stand may be too
strong for Palesnake.
I'm running out of time fast.
What should I?
Most of all, the newly
born entity will be...
The hell?
What'd you throw?
What did you do?
I asked you, what did
you just throw at me?
Discs are souls in
convenient material form.
They can be preserved for eternity.
However, if a disc enters
the body of someone dying,
it will simply fade out
and die along with them.
And no matter what you attempt to do,
you will never be able to resurrect it.
It's done.
That is Jotro's disc you've
been risking your life for!
Why waste time?
I have a better thought!
Anastasia's dying.
I could put it in his body instead.
I gouged the thing in.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to pull the disc out?
Or are you going to continue
with this ridiculous deathmatch?
To jettison Jotro's disc could indeed
be disastrous, but I fear nothing.
I've already read and memorized
how to get straight to heaven.
All that's left to do is execute it.
So Jolene Kujo, what's it going to be?
This is no longer an ultimate decision.
Your father's being dragged
to his death with Anastasia.
Aren't you upset?
Are you dead inside too?
All I really want and need now is
to obtain the newly born being.
Yes, I win!
As expected, she chose her father!
Now Spiral Stairs, The Beetle,
Abandoned Town, Fiktard,
Beetle, The Path to Dolorosa,
Beetle, Singularity, Giotto, Angel, Hydrangea,
Beetle, Singularity, Secret, Emperor!
Could it be your showing
interest in this will
you come to me quickly
of your own volition?
Will this be the new
beginning of everything?
Bless you my child now we can both enter
your world together hallelujah beloved Dio?
Anastasia!
No.
Am I too late?
This can't be. Please, no.
Tell me how.
How could this happen? Help! Somebody!
Is there anyone around?
I'm desperate. Guards! Over here! Hurry!
Hurry!
Can anyone hear me?
We need a doctor!
Hey!
Diver, drive.
Hey, FF, can you hear me?
Help us!
Choline's grieving. She's in pain.
This tragedy happened all because of you.
Damn it, I'm so cold and getting
colder with every passing moment.
My heart has almost stopped
beating entirely already.
Her father's disc was put
inside me, and if I die,
which appears very likely, it too
will certainly perish forever.
I truly struggle to remove it from my
body, but my consciousness is almost gone.
It appears you're disintegrating
and degenerating quickly, too.
I'll give you all I have
left, but you must do this.
I want you to use my intellect and
whatever small flicker remains of my life.
Use everything.
It's all yours now.
You're going to use that
to reach inside my body
and take the disc out
because Jolene needs it.
Only you, the plankton, can do this.
F .F., please, answer me.
Remember, you and I made a deal.
that you would hear
and obey all my orders.
I won't let you break our promise.
You're going to live on.
I don't care what you do to my body.
You have to hurry.
My consciousness is fading away.
No.
No, this cannot be happening. Anastasia!
You're wrong, Jolene.
Please don't worry.
It's not what you think.
The good news is...
Anastasia did it.
He recovered the disc. It's back.
FF? Wait!
Was that you?
Are you the one doing the talking?
I think what I was most afraid of...
was having to leave my
friends behind without
even having any time
to say goodbye to them.
But...
When the end finally came, I found
the strength and courage to do it.
Jolene, when Anastasia comes
to you, please tell him this.
Your body is yours alone.
I patched and healed your wounds with your
intelligence and your potent life force.
Hey, wait a minute!
What the hell are you talking about?
No! FF, wait! Goodbye, Jolene.
Thanks for everything.
My time here is finally up.
The one you know is FF will disappear.
What are you telling me?
This is crazy, I don't believe you!
Jolene, it's alright.
What you see right now is me.
This is my intellect, my soul.
And it's proof I was alive.
I'm gonna get your disc, FF's
disc, back from that priest.
No matter what, I promise you, you'll
come back to life and stay here!
But that'll be a different FF.
The me you know won't be in there.
This is the true me.
I could just say goodbye.
I couldn't have left
you without doing that!
Jolene.
It's gonna be okay.
And that's my promise to you.
I'm glad you finally got the disc back.
F .F., no.
Come in, F .F.
I can't track you. Do you copy? Over.
Where are you?
F .F., hey!
Come in, F .F. Acknowledge.
Huff, huff.
Place other than here,
although you think I smile
inside and all the while,
I'm wondering?
About my destiny!
I'm thinking about!
All the things!
I'd like to do!
In my life!
I'm a dreamer!
A distant dreamer!
Dreaming far away!
From today.
Thank you.